hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jerry
microkowski in this podcast I help
coaches mentors trainers authors and
thought leaders reach more people grow
their businesses and build their brands
to six seven and eight figures we help
thousands of people just like you get
the results they've always wanted and
one of the number one ways that we help
people do that is through paid
advertising and so today I want to talk
about how you can make more money with
your paid advertising and bring your
costs down with a little known fact
about how paid ads work now just briefly
if you want to understand this we have
gotten all of our clients in our
business through paid advertising all of
the businesses that we've helped grow to
eight figures have gotten their clients
through paid advertising and the clients
of mine that get the most results right
now also get theirs through paid
advertising so if you're watching this
you're saying well Jeremiah how do I how
do I learn how to do it without paid
advertising how do I do it without
paying no money well there's lots of
other great coaches out there that teach
that
I help people take their paid
advertising and amplify it to make tens
of millions of dollars that's why I say
if you just want to make a little bit of
money don't listen to me because you'll
probably get Super Rich by doing what I
talk about so here's the deal when you
run paid ads it's very easy to lose
money it's very easy for it not to
produce the return that you want and
that's okay
it's actually not okay because you don't
want to lose money but it's okay because
there's a solution to that is you don't
go at it blindly you don't run paid ads
without
a plan and a system and a way to make
sure that they produce results now how
can you make sure that your paid ads
produce results
most people and it honestly it takes me
like two three hours to get to this
point usually with people to where they
understand this I'm going to be skipping
a whole lot of what I usually do I have
like a two three hour presentation that
I do where I share this with people and
they finally have a light bulb go off
this aha moment to where they realize
that what I'm going to tell you is true
most of the people I meet sadly argue
and don't believe that what I'm about to
tell you is true because they have for
whatever reason been taught the complete
opposite
before you run paid ads
the most important thing
the most important two things
is
your offer
and your sales copy
the words that you use now there's tools
out there like chat GPT and Jasper that
are helping us write better sales copy
but please I beg of you don't use these
tools as a cop-out to stop thinking with
your own brain okay this is don't do
that
the only way that you're actually going
to make your offers work
is
by speaking to a very specific group of
people
and here's the fact that most people
don't realize about paid ads
I just shared this in a mastermind this
weekend
Facebook and Instagram and Tick Tock
will actually charge you more money
based on your copy
so one person's offer
that could be about you know one topic
let's just say I ran two offers and one
of them is about how you need an offer
okay and the other one is about how you
need to run your copy now both of these
are true when it comes to paid
advertising right let's just say I'm
going to run an ad and I'm going to say
I'm going to show you how to create
the author of your dreams it's going to
make you tons of money right and those
of you who are like well what's an offer
I don't know what an offer is an offer
is the thing that people sign up for
where they get on your email list where
when you run a paid ad they click it
and then you're presenting some kind of
a promise a presentation a webinar a
training something like that that's your
offer okay
that I could do another offer where I
says you know the number one thing you
need is sales copy you need to create
the best sales copy your sales copy is
what determines the cost all that
Facebook will actually charge me more
and I can't tell you which one they
would charge me more for but they would
charge me more
for one of these than the other they
will charge me more money sometimes 200
to 300
all the way up to a thousand percent
more 10x cost
and so it might literally cost me
a thousand dollars to get a client
with one
type of sales copy
and it might cost me a hundred dollars
to get a client with another type of
sales copy and all that changed was the
initial offer copy and Facebook decides
no we're gonna charge you 10 times as
much
and so this is why most people lose
money when they run their paid ads
because they're so focused on
um getting traffic
but they're sending traffic
to pages that Facebook is charging them
extra money for
so like does that does that make sense
to you
it's just basic economics in business
that you're not going to pay a thousand
dollars for what you could get for a
hundred bucks
right
and so where a lot of people and when
they don't understand how to use tools
like chat GPT and tools like Jasper to
write their copy and they don't have
offers that are specific enough to
connect with the prospect to connect
with who
is most likely to buy from them
and this is this is the part
where this is the part where that people
pay me the most amount of money for
as I help them
with this
is when you're not specific enough in
your copy
about who you help
they will charge you more money
this is why a lot of coaches and a lot
of mentors a lot of trainers while they
have a heart to help lots of people to
help a wide range of people
they can't reach their target client
because their copy is too vague too
General too generic it's reaching it's
casting too wide of a net okay and so
then the flip side of that is this
[Applause]
to make your paid ads actually work your
copy needs to be specific
not just to who is going to sign up
but it needs to be specific to one
specific type of person
your buyer
people
who are going to
spend money with you
which means
you actually have to exclude
and alienate and segregate and ostracize
not because you don't want to work with
them or could help them but because you
literally can't run a profitable
business the people who are not going to
buy from you
so like as a coach as a mentor
[Applause]
we have this belief
that this is our market right here that
we can reach okay
and and this is our Market that we can
help Okay outside of that like those are
probably people that are they have no
interest in what we're doing
but only about
this much of that market
is gonna buy from us
and the rest of this and this is just
from my experience of working for 19
years helping coaches actually 20 years
I'm at my 20th year now
21st year now but been doing it for 20
years
2003 is when I got into this industry
working with Danny Johnson and helping
my mom and Tom Challenge and and people
that helped me years ago I got my start
building funnels and marketing to drive
traffic to offers that would convert to
sales okay and then since then I've
immersed myself in the world
of mentorship coaching courses we used
to create DVD products and sell them to
the tune of tens of millions of dollars
and that's what I've done exclusively
for the last 20 years as my career and
I've gotten better and better and better
and honen honed in my craft and I've
gotten to the point where what I'm
teaching you right now that's what
people pay me the big bucks for that's
what people hire me tens of thousands of
dollars for to help them with
and so let's say that this segment is
your buyers right here this little green
part
all this red right here
while they might be lovely people
they might be nice people but there's
some rude people in there too right can
I get an amen but there might be some
nice people in this red
but what you have to do is you have to
actually exclude them
from your offer from your copy from your
language
is you have to exclude those people that
are in the red
in that tiny sliver
from working with you if you're watching
on the video and then the green portion
right here that we have marked is is
five percent you know five percent of
your Market is is likely to buy from you
so your copy needs to only speak to that
five percent
and completely and utterly not just
neglect not just exclude
not just ostracized and segregate and
alienate because literally I'm telling
you I get a lot of nasty letters because
people are like Jeremiah I'm
I would get make lots of money with you
and or or they write me and say you know
I'm a nice person and you're so nasty
Jeremiah for not letting me join your
coaching program when people apply we
turn away certain people and they get
really offended by that we have a a
qualification process that we use
and so but the truth is
those people who are not gonna buy from
you or maybe they were gonna buy for me
but they weren't a good fit right they
would get
uh disappointed
further along or your system just really
isn't and they they misunderstood right
I have people who think that
I've gotten really good after 20 years
of knowing who's a really good fit to
work with me and who's not and so some
people are like you you're assuming so
much about these people it's
evidence-based it's based off of
evidence
and so what you do is it becomes this
algorithmic equation
don't let that big word scare you
when you write sales copy
that is specifically written to your
buyers
okay
and you make sure to repel
anybody who is not going to get
great results with you isn't a good fit
maybe you know just based on that you're
going to notice some red flags about
certain people initially initially
you're going to have to test this out
and you might say well how do I know how
to do this I'm gonna I'm gonna share
that with you here at the end
and then I'm going to talk with you a
little bit about how you can use this to
bring your ads costs down one example of
this that we did we ran a campaign when
we were working with Rick Pino
and we ran two separate campaigns one
was written to
Christian songwriters right people of
Faith who write songs
the other campaign was written to
worship songwriters which worship is
actually a sub-genre of Christian music
so not all Christian songwriters make
worship music
there's a lot of country Christian Pop
Christian hip-hop all that right great
great people
and and truthfully Rick could help them
they know how to publish music in all
genres
when we ran our offer that was that the
copy was the only thing we changed one
word
Christian songwriter
we're like right we're gonna cast a
wider net we're gonna reach more people
the results were abysmal
it lost a ton of money
it seemed like a good idea but it lost a
ton of money
and so what we found is that actually by
turning away everybody who wasn't the
worship niche
his profits went up in his coaching
business in our business
when I
was advertising about a year ago we were
reaching all coaches all my mentors all
course creators
and some people wanted me to show them
how to do it without paid advertising
notice at the beginning what I said if
you want to learn how to do it without
paid advertising I'm probably not a good
fit for you there's other great coaches
that's me repelling away somebody who's
really not going to get much from me
who's really not going to get very much
results from me and so by you being
authentic and not filtering yourself and
specifically speaking to a a very
specific type of person that is not just
who you can help
but who's going to make an investment
and that's the most important part is
are they a potential buyer
and you write your offer copy that only
to the people who will buy from you
your advertising cost
will come down
and your sales and profits will go up
and so
when making an offer what we help people
optimize and do is to dial in their
offer copy and we're using tools like
chat GPT to do this we have different
methodologies and Frameworks that we
teach you how to do in my coaching
program that we teach you how to do even
on some of our free live events if you
ever see an ad with me running a free
live event that shows you how to launch
your offer or how to start a coaching
business or whatever that is those free
events walk you through a lot of those
processes step by step on how we're
doing that okay for for the sake of time
right now I try to make these podcast
episodes no more than 20 to 30 minutes
long I'm not going to go into those
details I do have a few episodes where I
did go into those details that you can
look back into okay but I'll tell you
this one of the best tools for using
artificial intelligence for sales copy
jasper.ai
jasper.ai is its essentially chat GPT
with a better algorithm on top of it
that writes better ad copy for your
Facebook ads better sales copy for your
landing pages we just did an intensive
yesterday where we helped our clients
craft their offer copy work on their
Niche work on their offer and put the
pieces together to get maximum results
in their business
and so
here's the thing I'd love for you to
join the waiting list of our group
coaching program if you haven't yet
the doors are not open you can't join my
coaching program right now
but I'd love for you to join the waiting
list for when we do open the doors to
jump into that
and to get the help that you need to
start to get more clients in your
business where I walk you through this
process I support you along the way
that's the number one thing that people
say is the difference maker with our
business see the podcasts obviously you
don't get much like you don't get any
support I'm just making episodes each
week I will provide you support though
if you comment on YouTube
if you comment on YouTube and enough
people leave a comment asking the same
questions I end up making new podcast
episodes and new offers so there is a
way to get support from me even in that
way otherwise Join one of the free
events that we're doing Join one of the
paid events that we're doing or consider
jumping into the client growth
accelerator our group coaching program
when the doors open again by joining the
waiting list
the number one thing that's going to
affect your offer that's going to affect
your ads that's going to affect your
cost per client acquisition is your copy
and making sure that it's laser targeted
to who's going to buy from you now how
can you figure that out
initially see I hope I didn't lose a lot
of people on the podcast it's funny what
happens when when I record a podcast
like this
whenever I talk about how you join the
waiting list and do all that people just
leave like we see that like people drop
off
sucks for them because I'm about to give
a strategy that they would have missed
which is great
so here's how you do this the feedback
loop is the number one way to write your
copy
we run virtual events Live Events
online
whether they be a one day workshop or a
three day or a five day
and when we run those workshops I have a
mechanism that surveys everybody who
registers and asks them what's their
biggest struggle and biggest problem and
I have a document with thousands of
those answers
and so then what I do is my copy this is
the secret
my my copy for my offers is literally
the answers that all those people gave
me
that's it
I I take the answers they gave me I
filter it through Jasper I filter it
through chat GPT
and then I create offers that just give
people what they already told me that
they're struggling with and that's how
we attract all of our clients and that's
what brings the cost down is by
generating a feedback loop by actually
creating a mechanism where people tell
you what they want so the idea is you
create a virtual event where you're
going to teach some kind of a topic we
base our topic off of that feedback loop
that people give us and this will be a
piece that I would add here
feedback
feedback loop
okay so these are the words that people
are saying of what they want to learn
what they're struggling with and and
what they want to take them to the next
level okay
so I got a little baby spittle here
you know how it is if you raising a new
baby
and so we take the feedback loop
and we filter it through the AI and
we're tweaking our copy just a little
bit just a little bit just a little bit
we've been running our offers for the
last year and we're still tweaking it we
helped my client Rick Pino get to over a
million dollars a month took us almost
18 months of doing this process
it it'll take about 12 to 18 months for
you to reach that seven to eight figure
level but you can reach six figures in
about 90 days most of the people who
start applying this system with us reach
that in about 90 days and then about a
year to two years after that
hit that seven figure level it's just
different levels to go to go from a
hundred thousand a year to a million a
year
and so how have we and our business been
able to generate over a hundred thousand
dollars a month we're on Pace in our
business to make over six figures
is by doing exactly this
and so when you create virtual events
you put them out there and people sign
up and register and then you survey
those people and ask them what are your
problems what are you struggling with
what would you like to learn and you
filter that into your copy and you
create another offer that's slightly
adjusted based off of what people say it
drives your costs down and raises your
profits all right so that's what you
want to do is you want to actually
create opportunities to listen to your
market for them to tell you what to put
in your copy and and then what you do is
you start to create mechanisms that
repel anybody who doesn't want what the
feedback loop people said so anybody who
is for me if you're a a staunch
perfectionist
if you're if you're a measure twice and
cut once type person to make sure that
it's just so the first time gosh you're
gonna get nothing out of working with me
because I tell you you need to launch
your offers recklessly you need to
launch them with Reckless abandon
because it's all an experiment it's all
a test there's no way for you to
guarantee that it's going to produce a
result that might not be what you want
to hear but it's the number one thing
that when people understand this that
you're marketing your offers when
reaching people it's all an experiment
it's all a test and perfectionism is the
greatest enemy of your goals
that's what makes them the most amount
of money and so listen if this has
helped you share it with somebody
jump into our waiting list enjoy your
life everybody we'll talk soon have a
good one
[Applause]